
Bandit Level 0
Level Goal

The goal of this level is for you to log into the game using SSH. The host to which you need to connect is bandit.labs.overthewire.org, on port 2220. The username is bandit0 and the password is bandit0. Once logged in, go to the Level 1 page to find out how to beat Level 1.

Commands you may need to solve this level
ssh

Helpful Reading Material
    Secure Shell (SSH) on Wikipedia
    How to use SSH on wikiHow



Sulotion:
    For connect to a remote server we can use ssh. 
ssh bandit0@bandit.labs.overthewire.org -p 2220
